// array with# and questions&answer and the options
let questions = [{
        numb: 1,
        question: "Which of the below is used in Javascript to insert special characters?",
        answer: '/',
        options: [
            '&',
            "/",
            '-',
            '%'
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "How do you find the number with the greatest value of  'a' and 'b'",
        answer: "Math.max(a,b)",
        options: [
            "Math.ceil(a,b)",
            "ceil(a,b)",
            "top(a,b)",
            "Math.max(a,b)"
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "JavaScript ignores extra spaces",
        answer: "True",
        options: [
            "True",
            "False",
            "This a easy one",
            "I am not sure!"
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "What is the correct way to call the random method on the Math global object?",
        answer: "Math.random()",
        options: [
            "random.Math()",
            "Math.random()",
            "math.random()",
            "Math(random)"
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "Which of the following functions is a valid function type that javascript supports?",
        answer: "1 and 2",
        options: [
            "A named function",
            "An Anonymous function",
            "1 and 2",
            "None of the above"
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "How can you add a comment in a JavaScript code?",
        answer: "//My JavaScript comment",
        options: [
            "/*My JavaScript comment*/",
            "//My JavaScript comment",
            '{_comment1": "my JavaScript comment}',
            'My JavaScript comment'
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "JavaScript is identical to Java?",
        answer: "False",
        options: [
            "True",
            "False",
            "You Tell Me!",
            "I am not sure!"
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "Which of the ways below is incorrect of instantiating a date?",
        answer: "new Date(seconds)",
        options: [
            'new Date(dateString)',
            'new Date()',
            'new Date(seconds)',
            'new Date(year, month, day, hours, minutes, seconds, milliseconds)'
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "How to round the number 15.2021 to a closer whole number?",
        answer: "Math.round(15.2021)",
        options: [
            "Math.round(15.2021)",
            "Math.rnd(15.2021)",
            "Math.sin(15.2021)",
            "Math.sqrt(15.2021)"
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "What is the code to get a random number between 5 and 9 inclusive?",
        answer: "Math.floor((Math.random()*5+5)",
        options: [
            "Math.floor((Math.random()*5+5)",
            "Math.floor((Math.random()*5+4)",
            "Math.floor((Math.random()*4+4)",
            "Math.floor((Math.random()*4+5)"
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 11,
        question: "How many parameters can be passed to a function?",
        answer: "1 for each argument",
        options: [
            "None",
            "As much as you want",
            "1 for each argument",
            "A maximum of 3"
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 12,
        question: "Which of the following is not a mouse event?",
        answer: "onmousescroller",
        options: [
            "onclick",
            "onmouse",
            "onbutton",
            "onmousescroller"
        ]
    },

];